<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Geoff Holden</title>
    <link>http://geoffholden.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Geoff Holden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 11:38:28 -0230</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://geoffholden.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Tea Drinker</title>
      <link>http://geoffholden.com/2016/03/becoming_a_tea_drinker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 11:38:28 -0230</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geoffholden.com/2016/03/becoming_a_tea_drinker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently started drinking tea. Well, that&amp;rsquo;s not &lt;em&gt;entirely&lt;/em&gt; true&amp;mdash;I recently started drinking tisane (herbal tea), specifically peppermint tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started drinking peppermint because it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to have some medicinal properties, particularly in relieving IBS symptoms. At first I treated it as a potential treatment; I didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy drinking it, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t horrible. But over the past several weeks, the taste has really grown on me, and I now look forward to sitting down with my cuppa. I&amp;rsquo;m actually enjoying it enough that I&amp;rsquo;ve started stashing a couple of tea bags in my coat or bag, so that I can have a cup when I&amp;rsquo;m not home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not completely sold on whether it&amp;rsquo;s actually having any effect or not, but it is replacing a lot of the less healthy drinks in my diet, which is not a bad thing. I&amp;rsquo;m also finding it to a good thing socially. I was never a coffee or tea drinker, as I gave up caffeine so long ago that I never started drinking either. This was always a little awkward, because so many people meet for coffee, at coffee shops, etc. just sitting there, not drinking anything was always a little odd. So, overall, I believe starting to drink tea has provided small improvements to my life, both health-wise and socially.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

